Guide to the Herbert Aptheker Papers, 1842-1999, (bulk 1934-1994)
Department of Special Collections
- Series 1. Correspondence
  - AIMS correspondence: D, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - AIMS correspondence: D, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - AIMS correspondence: E, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - AIMS correspondence: F, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - AIMS correspondence: G, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - AIMS correspondence: H, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - AIMS correspondence: I, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - AIMS correspondence: J, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - AIMS correspondence: K, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - AIMS correspondence: L, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - AIMS correspondence: L, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - AIMS correspondence: M, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - AIMS correspondence: N - O, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - AIMS correspondence: P, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - AIMS correspondence: R, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - AIMS correspondence: R, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - AIMS correspondence: S, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - AIMS correspondence: S, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - AIMS correspondence: S, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - AIMS correspondence: T, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - AIMS correspondence: U - V, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - AIMS correspondence: W, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - AIMS correspondence: Y, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - A, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - A, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - C, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - C, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - D, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - E - F, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - G, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - H, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - I, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - J, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - K, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - L, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - M, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - N - O, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - P - Q, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - R, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - S, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - S, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - T, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - T, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - W, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - X - Z, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - AIMS correspondence: A, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - AIMS correspondence: B, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - AIMS correspondence: C, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - AIMS correspondence: D, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - AIMS correspondence: D, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - AIMS correspondence: F, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - AIMS correspondence: G, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - AIMS correspondence: G, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - AIMS correspondence: H, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - AIMS correspondence: I - J, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - AIMS correspondence: K, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - AIMS correspondence: L, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - AIMS correspondence: L, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - AIMS correspondence: L, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - AIMS correspondence: M, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - AIMS correspondence: N, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - AIMS correspondence: O, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - AIMS correspondence: P - Q, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - AIMS correspondence: S, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - AIMS correspondence: S, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - AIMS correspondence: T, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - AIMS correspondence: T, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - AIMS correspondence: W, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - AIMS correspondence: W, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - AIMS correspondence: Y - Z, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - A, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Aptheker, Bettina
  - A, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - B, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - B, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - B, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - B, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - C, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - C, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - C, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - C, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - D, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - D, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - D, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - D, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - D, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - E, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - F, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - F, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - F, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - G, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - G, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - G, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - H, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - H, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - H, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - I, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - J, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - K, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - K, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - L, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - L, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - L, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - L, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - M, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - M, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - M, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - M, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - N, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - O, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - P, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - P, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - P, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - R, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - R, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - R, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - R, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - S, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - S, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - S, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - S, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - S, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - T, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - T, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - U, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - V, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - W, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - W, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - W, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - W, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - W, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Y, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Z, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - AIMS correspondence: A, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - AIMS correspondence: B, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - AIMS correspondence: B, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - AIMS correspondence: C, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - AIMS correspondence: C, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - AIMS correspondence: D, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - AIMS correspondence: E, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - AIMS correspondence: F, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - AIMS correspondence: G, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - AIMS correspondence: H, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - AIMS correspondence: H, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - AIMS correspondence: I - J, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - AIMS correspondence: K, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - AIMS correspondence: K, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - AIMS correspondence: L, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - AIMS correspondence: M, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - AIMS correspondence: N - O, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - AIMS correspondence: P, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - AIMS correspondence: R, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - AIMS correspondence: S, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - AIMS correspondence: S, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - AIMS correspondence: S, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    Contains Twilight of our past: an inquiry into the origins of Black History / Sterling Stuckey. -- 1 tms (51 p.)
  - AIMS correspondence: S, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - AIMS correspondence: T, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - AIMS correspondence: V, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - AIMS correspondence: W, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - AIMS correspondence: Y - Z, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - A, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - B, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - B, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - B, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - C, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - C, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - C, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - D, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - D, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - E, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - F, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - G, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - H, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - H, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - H, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - J, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Jackson, George, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - K, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - K, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - L, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - L, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - M, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - M, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - M, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - N, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - O, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - P, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - R, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - S, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - S, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - S, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - T, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - U - V, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - W, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - W, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - X - Z, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - A, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Ba - Bl, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Bo - Bu, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Ca - Ch, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Ci - Co, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Co - Cu, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - D, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Da - Do, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Dr - Du, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - E, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - F, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Ga - Go, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Gr - Gu, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Ha, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - He - Hy, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - I, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - J, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Ka - Ke, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Ki - Ku, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Kraus, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - La - Li, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Lo - Lu, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Ma - Mh, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Massachusetts, University of. Press, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    Contains correspondence regarding W.E.B. DuBois' 7 CRITIQUES OF NEGRO EDUCATION. Also contains correspondence from Malcolm Call re: LETTERS OF W.E.B. DUBOIS.
    Stein, Leona Wright, Paul
  - Mi - Mu, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - N, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - O, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Pa - Pl, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Po - Pu, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Ra - Re, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Ri - Ry, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Sa - Sl, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Sm - St, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - T, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - V, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Wa - Wh, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Wi, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Wo - Wr, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Y - Z, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - AIMS correspondence: A, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - AIMS correspondence: B, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - AIMS correspondence: C, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - AIMS correspondence: D, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - AIMS correspondence: F, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - AIMS correspondence: G, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - AIMS correspondence: H, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - AIMS correspondence: I, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - AIMS correspondence: J, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - AIMS correspondence: K, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - AIMS correspondence: L, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - AIMS correspondence: M, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - AIMS correspondence: University of Massachusetts Press correspondence re: THE EDUCATION OF BLACK PEOPLE and W.E.B. DuBois' CORRESPONDENCE [1 of 2], 1973 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - AIMS correspondence: University of Massachusetts Press correspondence re: THE EDUCATION OF BLACK PEOPLE and W.E.B. DuBois' CORRESPONDENCE [2 of 2], 1973 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - AIMS correspondence: N, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - AIMS correspondence: P, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - AIMS correspondence: R, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - AIMS correspondence: S, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - AIMS correspondence: T, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - AIMS correspondence: U, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - AIMS correspondence: V, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - AIMS correspondence: W, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - AIMS correspondence: Y, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - A, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - B, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - C, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - C, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - C, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - C, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - D, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - D, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - E - F, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - G, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - G, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - H, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - H, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - I, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - J, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - K, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - K, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - L, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - M, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - M, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - M, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - N, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - O, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - P, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - R, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - R, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - S, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - S, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - T, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - U - V, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - W, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - X - Z, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - A, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - B, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - B, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - B, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - C, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - C, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - C, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - C, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - D, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - D, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - E, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - F, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - F, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - G, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - G, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - G, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - H, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - H, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - H, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - H, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - I, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - J, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - K, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Kraus, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - L, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - L, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - M, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    University of Massachusetts Press
  - M, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - M, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - M, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - M, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - N, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - O, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - P, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - P, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - P, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Q, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - R, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - R, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - S, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - S, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - S, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - S, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - S, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - T, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - T, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - U, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - V, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - W, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - W, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - W, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - W, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - X - Z, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - A, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - B, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - B, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - C, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - D, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - E, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - F, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - G, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - G, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - H, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - H, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - H, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - I, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - J, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - K, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Kraus, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - L, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - L, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    Lawrence, Ken
  - L, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - L, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - L, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - M, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - M, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - M, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - M, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - M, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - N, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - O, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - P, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - P, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - P, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    Pittman, John
  - P - Q, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Ra - Rec, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Ree - Ry, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - S, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - S, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - S, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - T, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - T, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - U - V, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - W, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - W, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Y, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    Yale University
  - C - D, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - F, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - G, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - H - J, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - K - L, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - M, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - N, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - P, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - R, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - S, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - T - V, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - W, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - A, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - A, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - B, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - B, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - B, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - C, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - C, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - D, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - D, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - E, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - F, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - F, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - G, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - G, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - G, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - G, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - H, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - H, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - H, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - I, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - J, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - K, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - K, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - L, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - L, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - L, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - M, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - M, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - M, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - M, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - N, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - N, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - O, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - P, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - P, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - P, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Q, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - R, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - R, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - R, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - S, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - S, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - S, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - S, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - S, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - T, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - T, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - U - V, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - W, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - W, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Y - Z, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Staughton - Nat Turner materials, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - A, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - B, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - C, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - D, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - E, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - F, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - G, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - H, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - I, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - J, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - K, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - L, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - M, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - N, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - O, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - P, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - R, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - S, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - S, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - T, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - U, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - V, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - W, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Y, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Z, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - A, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - B, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - C [C - Cohen], 1977 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - C [Coll - Cz], 1977 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - D, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - E, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - F, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - G, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - H, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - I, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - J, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - K, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - L, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - M, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - N, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - O, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - P, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - R, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - S [S - Stein], 1977 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - S [Ster - Stu], 1977 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - T, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - W, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Y, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Z, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified correspondence, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - A, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Ba - Bl, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Blanca Films (Isla Negra), 1978 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    Includes 30 pp tms for ON COMPANY BUSINESS
  - Bo - Bu, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Braestrup, Peter [Ed., The Wilson Quarterly], 1978 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    Includes proofs of Spring 1978 issue
  - Ca - Ci, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Co - Cu, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - D, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - E, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - F, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - G, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - H, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - I, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - J, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - K, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - L, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Lemisch, Jesse - Staughton Lynd correspondence, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - M, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - M, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - N, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - O, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - P, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - R, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - S, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - S, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - S, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - T, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - V, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - W, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Y, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Z, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - A, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - B, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - C, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - D, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - E, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - F, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - G, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - H, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - H, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - I, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - J, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - K, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - L, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - M, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - M, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - N, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - O, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - P, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - R, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - S, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - T, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - U - W, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Y, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Z, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Unidentified, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - A, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - B, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - C, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - D, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - E - F, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - G, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - H, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - I - J, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - K, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - L, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Ma - Mc, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Mi - Mz, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - N, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - P, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Q - R, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Sa - Sl, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Sm - Su, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - T - U, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - W, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Y - Z, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Unidentified, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, [197-] (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - A, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - B, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - C, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - C, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - D, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - E, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - F, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - G, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - G, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - H, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - H, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - J, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - K, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - L, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - M, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - M, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - M, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - N, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - O, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - P, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - R, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - S, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - S, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - S, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Sanders, Irwin re: Abolitionist movement volume,, 1980; 1986 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - T, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - U, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - W, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - X - Z, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - A, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Ba - Beck, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Belgum, Harold, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Bell - Bo, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Bra - Brook, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Brown, Lloyd L., 1981 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Bry - Bu, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Ca - Ce, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Ch - Col, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Con - Cu, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - D, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - E, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - FBI - Fo, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Foner, Philip, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Fr - Fu, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Ga - Gi, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Goggin, Jacqueline, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Gol - Gu, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Ha, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Hill, Robert A., 1981 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Ho - Hu, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - I, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - J, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - K, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Lab - Law, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Le - Lo, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Ma, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Me - Moran, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 2)